<?xml version="1.0"?>
<info>
    <id>search</id>
    <name>Advanced Search</name>
    <description>
	<p>
	    Purpose: Provides users with search capabilities of all objects
	    in ownCloud and a simple user interface to interact with them.
	</p>
	<p>
	    Environment: Designed for ownCloud 5.0 and above. Search extends
	    only to objects created by apps in the github 'app' repository; to make your
	    objects available for search, see the Developers section.
	</p>
	<p>
	    Domain: The app only interacts with search providers extending
	    OC_Search_Provider and search results extending OC_Search_Result.
	</p>
	<p>
	    Technologies: The application has the option to store results in a
	    Lucene database, allowing complex queries. Otherwise, results will
	    be pulled from the available search providers.
	</p>
	<p>
	    Formats: Search results must extend OC_Search_Result; public 
	    properties of the search result will be available in the search
	    application. Also, the search application will call formatToHtml()
	    prior to displaying any search result data, giving the developer a 
	    chance to add HTML to any properties.
	</p>
	<p>
	    Options: The Lucene database can be turned on and off from the 
	    'Personal' tab. In the future, the search form will contain options
	    to select result types.
	</p>
	<p>
	    Running time: Because indexing for the Lucene database may take some
	    time, this is scheduled as a background task for ownCloud's 'cron'
	    system.
	</p>
	<p>
	    Accuracy: not tests created at this time.
	</p>
	<p>
	    Developers: The main line of effort of the program is to pull search
	    results from search providers and present them as HTML in a series
	    of tables, one for each result type. The 'index.php' file handles
	    this functionality with the help of the 'templates' files.
	</p>
	<p>
	    When using the Lucene database, results must first be indexed in the
	    database; this ocurrs via hooks when an object is created, modified,
	    deleted, etc. The hook functions add indexing to the queue of 
	    background tasks.
	</p>
	<p>
	    This project is still in beta testing.
	</p>
    </description>
    <licence>AGPL</licence>
    <author>Andrew Brown</author>
    <require>5.0</require>
    <shipped>false</shipped>
    <standalone/>
    <default_enable/>
    <types>
        <filesystem/>
    </types>
</info>
